Register of the G. William Gahagan papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed Matter, 1942-1952, undated (Box 7)
  - ABC's of Scapegoating, Harvard University, Department of Psychology, undated (Box-folder 7: 14)
  - G.I. Comics, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 15)
  - Meet the Anzacs! by W. L. Holland and Phillip E. Lilienthal, American Council of Pacific Relations, 1942 (Box-folder 7: 16)
  - Time, overseas service editions, 1943, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 17)
    Contains two special editions printed for the armed forces from September 13, 1943 and February 12, 1945.